[{"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['hat', 'hat', 'hat'];['shoes', 'shoes', 'shoes'];['surface', 'surface', 'surface']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['skirt', 'skirt', 'skirt'];['surface', 'surface', 'surface'];['orb', 'orb', 'orb']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/紫色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['skirt', 'skirt', 'skirt'];['shoes', 'shoes', 'shoes'];['orb', 'orb', 'orb']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/紫色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['hat', 'hat', 'hat'];['skirt', 'skirt', 'skirt'];['shoes', 'shoes', 'shoes']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/紫色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['skirt', 'skirt', 'skirt'];['shoes', 'shoes', 'shoes'];['orb', 'orb', 'orb']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/紫色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['hat', 'hat', 'hat'];['skirt', 'skirt', 'skirt'];['surface', 'surface', 'surface']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['shoes', 'shoes', 'shoes'];['orb', 'orb', 'orb'];['hat', 'hat', 'hat']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['orb', 'orb', 'orb'];['surface', 'surface', 'surface'];['shoes', 'shoes', 'shoes']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/紫色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['skirt', 'skirt', 'skirt'];['shoes', 'shoes', 'shoes'];['hat', 'hat', 'hat']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['surface', 'surface', 'surface'];['shoes', 'shoes', 'shoes'];['hat', 'hat', 'hat']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['shoes', 'shoes', 'shoes'];['orb', 'orb', 'orb'];['surface', 'surface', 'surface']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/紫色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['hat', 'hat', 'hat'];['skirt', 'skirt', 'skirt'];['orb', 'orb', 'orb']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/紫色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_2.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['surface', 'surface', 'surface'];['orb', 'orb', 'orb'];['skirt', 'skirt', 'skirt']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['orb', 'orb', 'orb'];['hat', 'hat', 'hat'];['surface', 'surface', 'surface']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/紫色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['orb', 'orb', 'orb'];['hat', 'hat', 'hat'];['skirt', 'skirt', 'skirt']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "拖一拖，把下面物品分为三类。", "content": [{"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "shoes", "src": "v2/通用/鞋靴/鞋子_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-drag"}], "answers": "{['shoes', 'shoes', 'shoes'];['hat', 'hat', 'hat'];['surface', 'surface', 'surface']}", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-3"}]